

# **GEERTHIKA LAKSHMANAN**

**UI/UX** Designer

P: +91 9095232109, +91 8248272742

E: argeerthi14@gmail.com

Location: 124B, Sivaganga 630301, TN, India.

https://www.behance.net/geerthi

https://www.linkedin.com/in/geerthika

## **EDUCATION**

2022

UI/UX Design, Designboat Bootcamp, Bangalore, India

2015-2020

**B.Arch**, Department of Architecture, Anna University, Chennai, India

## **SKILLS**

Software	Design
Figma	Design Research
Sketch	User Interface
Invision	Web Design
SketchUp 3D	Wireframing
Adobe XD	UX Design
Adobe Photoshop	Prototype
Adobe Illustrator	Branding
Adobe Indesign	Marketing Design

## **Programming**

HTML CSS Bootstrap

**JavaScript** 

# **LANGUAGES**

English, Tami, Hindi

# **ABOUT**

I am a passionate and creative UI/UX designer with an architecture background. I've worked on a set of projects, working from research to production, that includes iOS, Android, web, B2C, user research, data visualization, and marketing design. Learning to code HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and JS helped me to have better control of design and improved my communication with teams.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

(June 2022 - Present)

#### **UI UX Designer**

Redd Experience Design, Bangalore - Worked on the cryto web projects, prepared moodboards for DEX of Persistence One. In charge of Persistence One's marketing collateral deliverables, including the pitch deck, BNB Deck, and PStake. Prepared design moodboards and final products, UI interface, research and study. I contributed to the task of redesigning the marketing collaterals for the brand Persistence One, which is a Dubai-based company.

(June 2021 - April 2022)

## **UI UX Freelance Designer**

Worked on UI products, with design research, wireframe, prototype and branding. Collaboration with startsups in Design Branding, Logo, Event Posters, Concept art, Colour theory, Social media management. (Collaboration: Lacasa Studio, Kanoji Design studio, Design Partners, Chui Huay Lim Teochew Cusine, Singapore, Black Architects)

(Jan 2020 - Oct 2021)

## Junior Designer

HCP design Planning & Management pvt.ltd, Ahmedabad - Worked on the project of 'Central Vista Redevelopment of India, Delhi'. Involved in Indian government presentation deliverables.

(Jan 2019 - Oct 2021)

# Internship

SR+A Architects, Mumbai - Architecture Internship